This video introduces the AI model posture generator function for everyone.
In the newly released 2025.0 version, we have launched a powerful new function, the AI model posture generator.
This new function allows us to manually adjust the joints without any need to input text prompt or upload images.
AI will be able to simply and quickly generate the model posture you want.
First, select the virtual model, AI model posture generator in the menu bar.
If there is a virtual model or costume in the 3D window of the software, a warning window will pop up.
Ask if you want to continue running the AI model posture generator.
If you choose to run, all virtual models and costumes in the 3D window will be deleted.
Before choosing to run, please save the current work content or open a new project file.
In the AI model posture generator window, there are two methods to choose from, prompt words and images.
When using prompt words, you can input the necessary description or select a keyword to generate images.
When using images, you can upload the selected posture image file yourself and directly generate the posture according to the image.
Next, let's take a look at how the AI model posture generator is operated.
Let's take a look at how to use the prompt words.
The first option is gender. You can choose between women or men according to your needs.
Next is the key word prompt.
You can enter the description text you want to generate.
On the right side of the prompt window, there are three different icons representing different functions.
The first is the key word suggestion.
After clicking it, it will display the recommended list of key words that we can use.
When clicking one of the key words, it will automatically be added to the prompt window and the key word will be displayed as a blue font.
If you want to delete the key word, you only need to click the X on the right side of the key word under the prompt window.
Or in the key word suggestion, click the key word again.
You can cancel the selection of the selected key word.
Even if you use the same prompt, the AI model posture generator will generate different new images every time.
But if you activate the second big arrow, which is the key word function to keep the input, it will keep the image generated before as much as possible.
At the same time, use the new key word prompt to generate updates.
The third type of arrow is random generation.
When you want to find inspiration or ideas, you can use it.
If you want to change the prompt, you can click the icon in the upper right corner of the prompt window, similar to the eraser, and clear the prompt to reset all the content.
Or use the key word function to keep the input.
For the existing prompt, make detailed adjustments.
After editing, click Start Generation.
The AI model posture generator will create images based on the prompt.
If you are satisfied with the generated image, please click Save.
It can be exported as a posture file for further use.
Now let's follow the example.
Now let's create a new model posture according to the steps we just introduced.
First, we will set the gender as male.
Then, in the list of keywords recommended by the key word prompt, select the keyword tennis.
This means that we will eventually show the posture of a tennis player.
Next, we will describe the complete text in detail.
Enter a tennis player's side wave in the prompt box.
Show the tension of speed and the player.
Everything is ready.
Click Start Generation to create the image.
If you like the image generated, you can click Start Generation at the bottom.
Apply the posture in the image as a virtual model posture.
If you want to re-enter the description text in the prompt box, you can click Clear Prompt.
If you just need to make some adjustments, you can open the key word to keep the input and then update the prompt.
Click Start Generation.
It will use the current image as the basis for the new image generated again.
For example, we want to raise the arm on the basis of the current image.
We first click the key word to keep the input.
Then, in the prompt box, add a new short word to modify the posture.
Raise the arm higher.
For example, raise your arm up.
Once the final image is generated, it reflects the posture you want.
Click Start Generation at the bottom of the window.
Change the image posture to a virtual model posture.
Click History Record on the right side of the window.
You can check it out.
You can check all the images generated in it.
If there is an image you want to save in the history record, you can select it directly and then click Save in the upper right corner.
Set up the save path.
After clicking Save, a PNG-shaped image will be saved.
You can also select all the images and save all the images.
Click Save after there is no problem.
The current posture will be translated into a posture file for further use.
Now let's see how to use the existing image file.
Create a virtual model posture.
We select a woman and then click the upload button.
Select the image to be applied and click open.
The image will be added.
After successfully adding the image file, click on the bottom of the window to start generating.
Change the image to a model posture.
After confirming that the generated posture is fine, click Save and save it as a posture file.
Next, let's apply the saved posture file to the virtual model.
Close the window of the AI model posture generator.
You can import any female model from the library.
Or open the project file you want to apply the posture.
Then click on the file to open the posture.
Select the just saved posture file and open it.
In the open posture window that is displayed,
you can use the posture file after confirming that the virtual model has been applied.
Use the AI model posture generator.
All you need is a line of text or a reference image.
The reference image can be easily created.
It is a posture that is natural and expressive when used in fashion, clothing, and exercise.